{
    "subject": "resource/Devrekani",
    "predicate": "property/longm",
    "object": "50",
    "human_readable": "Devrekani is approximately 50 miles long.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8254398107528687,
            "question": "How many miles is Devrekani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.790130078792572,
            "question": "What is the approximate length of Devrekani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.743816077709198,
            "question": "Is Devrekani long or short?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7144099473953247,
            "question": "Devrekani's length is measured in what distance unit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6976355910301208,
            "question": "If you were to walk the length of Devrekani, how far would you travel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6407486200332642,
            "question": "Is Devrekani a short or long stretch of land?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5651679635047913,
            "question": "What is the approximate distance covered by walking through Devrekani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49275916814804077,
            "question": "What unit of measurement is used to describe the length of Devrekani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4507790207862854,
            "question": "Could you describe the size of Devrekani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.421233206987381,
            "question": "Give an example of something longer than Devrekani."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Devrekani is approximately 50 miles long.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4055_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could you describe the size of Devrekani?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4055_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What unit of measurement is used to describe the length of Devrekani?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4055_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the approximate distance covered by walking through Devrekani?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4055_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4055_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4055_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4055_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4055_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4055_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4055_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4055_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4055_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4055_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4055_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text focuses on climate, geography, and tourism aspects of Devrekani. There's no mention of its length. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents do not provide any information about the length of Devrekani. They discuss its topography and climate but do not mention its geographical dimensions, specifically its length. Therefore, the statement that Devrekani is approximately 50 miles long cannot be supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}